JORGE LUIS DE LOS SANTOS REYES

• DETAILS •

Canada 226-346-1008 jorge20080@hotmail.com

• LINKS •

LinkedIn

• SKILLS •

JavaScript

TypeScript

React

C#

Node.js

SQL

Bootstrap

PHP

jQuery

CSS

HTML

Git

HTML & CSS

Java

Selenium

Nunit

Xunit

• LANGUAGES •

Spanish

English

PROFILE

I am a professional on the IT field, able to adapt to different environments and work under pressure. Love working as a team in a way to achieve the goals of the company, always following the strategies and guidelines provided by the organization. During my professional career I have been able to develop mostly in the QA field where I have gone from some basic manual testing to some advanced automated testing. I have over 6 years of experience in software quality assurance.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

QA Automation Engineer at Megsoft, Santo Domingo

June 2021 — Present

- Tracked, documented, and reported quality levels and perform analysis for quality improvement initiatives.
- Create and maintain our automation framework using selenium with C# and NUnit.
- Continuously add test cases to our set of test cases for automation.
- Write, design, and execute automated tests by creating scripts that run testing functions automatically
- Maximize test coverage for the most critical features of the system
- Determine the priority for test scenarios and create execution plans to implement these scenarios

Software Quality Assurance Engineer at FlashParking, Santo Domingo

July 2019 — June 2021

- Performed routine inspections of finished products to check for defects and other problems before these products are shipped for distribution.
- Tracked, documented, and reported quality levels and perform analysis for quality improvement initiatives.
- Monitored risk-management procedures, and maintained and analyzed problem logs to identify and reported recurring issues to management and product development
- Coordinated investigation of quality issues with customers and suppliers.
- Wrote clean, high-quality scripts that test product functionality automatically.
- Conducted various tests for systems, networks, applications, databases, software.
- Logged and documented errors in the tracking system.
- Developed the best automation solutions based on the clients' requirements.

Software Quality Assurance Analyst at Kore Wireless, Santo Domingo

January 2017 — July 2019

- Test Driven Development and regression testing
- Affirmed that software functions according to functional and user requirements
- Improved and extended test frameworks and automated test sets
- · Reported all defects in Jira
- · Prepared, maintained and executed system test plans.

Application Tech Support at Kore Wireless, Santo Domingo

December 2015 — January 2017

- Followed policies and procedures related to application methods and quality standards at all times.
- Identified hardware and software solutions.
- · Troubleshooted technical issues.
- · Diagnosed and repaired faults.

Food Service Lead at Six Flags Great America, Waukegan

May 2015 — August 2015

- Placed orders for necessary goods such as food, kitchen tools, and cleaning products.
- Assisted with food preparations prior to service.
- Handled food with sanitation and safety in mind.
- Aimed to keep food waste to a minimum by using proper food storage and recycling techniques.

Customer Service Representative at ACS Xerox, Santo Domingo

April 2013 — April 2015

- Brought forth a self-motivated attitude.
- Helped to achieve increases in sales.
- Communicated effectively with colleagues and superiors.
- Attended workshops and conferences centered around increasing customer service skills.
- Accurately verified information and updated information databases as necessary.

EDUCATION

Networking Technologist, ITLA, Santo Domingo

October 2012 — August 2014

System Engineering, UNICDA, Santo Domingo

October 2014 — January 2021

 $\label{thm:condition} \textbf{Web Development and Internet Applications Diploma, St. Clair College, Windsor, ON}$

September 2022 — Present

COURSES

English Course, APEC

2007 - 2009

English as a second language, ITLA

2010 - 2011

Software testing certified course, XAUREO

September 2019 — December 2019

REFERENCES

Ruddy Castro from Kore Wireless

 $ruddy_castro025@hotmail.com \cdot 8296651924$

Miguel Angel Arzeno from FLASH

miguelarzeno@gmail.com · 8099056385

Moises Fernandez from Kore Wireless

mfernandez_marte@hotmail.com · 6786835646